 <Project name="Stutility">
	 <Developer>Hayford Edoonu (Edon)</Developer>
 	<Aim>
		To bring most things that students(of UCC) usually need or do like taking notes,
		visiting their portals, UCC-elearning sites, checking timetable, etc all into one app
		for easy accessibility.
	</Aim>
 	<Versions>
 		<v1.1 code="1">
 			<Started>Started: 28th October, 2021, 15:9p </Started>
 			<Ended>20th December, 2021, 16:43</Ended>
 			<Activities>
				Developed this version based on the main version which is in Java into Kotlin,
				implemented few Material Design guides and components,
				Improved the layout which was static into relatively responsive one,
				implemented recycler view with custom adapter for lists that changed on runtime
				(eg. List of other useful websites),
				implemented webview in the app instead of opening external web browser,
				implemented toolbars and menus (eg. in timetable activity),
				implemented alert dialogs.
				Refreshed and learnt lots about basic android development including SQLite database using SQLiteHelper class.
				Data classes helped a lot in creating models of objects
			</Activities>
 		</v1.1>
 		<v1.2.0 code="2">
 			<Started>1st January, 2022, 16:58, </Started>
 			<Ended>4th January, 2022, around 16:00</Ended>
 			<Activities>
 				Added a Todo list aspect to the app. Implemented custom dialog and checkboxes.
				Stored offline with SLite database.
 			</Activities>
 		</v1.2.0>
		<v1.2.1 code="3">
			<Started>7th January, 2022, 15:50</Started>
			<Ended> 7th January, 2022, 20: 17</Ended>
			<Activities>
				Improve the design of the web browser part of the app
				Improved design of todo items, implemented popup menu for each item
				for the edit and delete
				Gave a tint background color to the items based on its priority color
				implemented paint flags to the done todos (strike through)
			</Activities>
		</v1.2.1>
		<v1.2.2 code="4">
			<Started>8th January, 2022, 8:39</Started>
			<Ended> 8th January, 2022, 8:48</Ended>
			<Activities>
				Added zoom controls to the webview (pinch to zoom)
				Removed night mode theme and forced theme to be light even in dark mode
				settings of host device
			</Activities>
		</v1.2.2>
		<v1.2.3 code="5">
			<Started>10th January, 2022, 11:50</Started>
			<Ended> 10th January, 2022, 12:16</Ended>
			<Activities>
				Modified look of custom todo dialog
				Making website fit to screen of device in the webview
				Fixed height of webview top cardView(containing back, forward and refresh buttons)
			</Activities>
		</v1.2.3>
	 <v1.2.4 code="6">
		 <Started>25th February, 2022, 11:20</Started>
		 <Ended> 27th February, 2022, 20:10</Ended>
		 <Activities>
			 Used recycler view in the MainActivity (dashboard) to implement the list
			 which is more efficient and reduced the number of lines of code to view the dashboard
			 Joined the courses and timetable tables in the Lecture database and set update and delete constraints
			 Check existence of course before saving new one to avoid repetition
		 </Activities>
	 </v1.2.4>
 </Versions>
 </Project>